codeship.io 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy | Codeship

Codeship Inc., directly or through its affiliate Railsonfire Limited (in either case, “Codeship”), operates several websites including codeship.io, codeship.com, and other similar sites offering or promoting the Codeship services. These sites are governed by Codeship’sTerms of Service, of which this Privacy Policy is a part and is incorporated by reference therein.

Please read these terms carefully, and check back frequently. Our lawyer goes to a lot of trouble to write this stuff and we think he’s sad that no one reads them. Or maybe he’s just sad in general. We don’t know. But regardless, we hope you find our policy with respect to your privacy to be both reasonable and understandable.

### ... or in other words ...

#### Overview

At Codeship, we take privacy – and in particular, **your** privacy – extremely seriously. We operate under a few basic principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact us.

####  Overview

Codeship is a service created **by** developers, **for** developers. We know how important privacy is for you, because it’s important for us.

That’s why we’re committed to ensuring the information we collect from you – and that we ask that you provide to us from time to time – is both necessary and reasonable to provide you with the best services possible.

#### Website visitors

Like most website operators, Codeship collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available – e.g. browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. We do this for purposes of understanding and improving our users’ experience. While we may, from time to time, make certain aggregate user information available (e.g. releasing information on our site regarding user trends and site analytics), we will never release any information identifying any individual site visitor or sell or transfer any of this information other than as described below.

####  Website visitors

We want you to have the best possible user experience when you visit our site(s). In order to do so, we gather, monitor and analyze certain general information from each site visitor. We don’t sell this information make it available to anyone other than our internal UX folks, though we may occasionally publish aggregate stats on our site if we’re feeling particularly chuffed about something.

#### Gathering of personally-identifying information

Certain visitors to Codeship’s websites may elect to sign up to use Codeship’s services offered via one or more sites. In these instances, we are required to verify that you are indeed an actual person, and that you are (and will continue to be) in compliance with Codeship’sTerms and Conditions. In order to do so, we may ask that you provide us with certain personally-identifying information for such purposes. The amount and type of information that Codeship gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at codeship.com to provide an email address. Those who engage in transactions with Codeship – by purchasing access to the premium features – are asked to provide additional information, including (as necessary) personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Codeship collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the interaction. Codeship does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Codeship discloses personally-identifying information (actual or potential) only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations (i) that need to know that information in order to process it on Codeship’s behalf or to provide services available at Codeship’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Codeship’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Codeship will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Codeship discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Codeship believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Codeship, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Codeship website and have supplied your email address, Codeship may occasionally send you notices to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up-to-date with what’s going on with Codeship and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Codeship takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

####  Gathering of personally-identifying information

Yes, if you sign up for certain Codeship services then you’ll need to provide certain information to ensure you’re a real human being. And also to ensure you can pay (if applicable) for the services you’ve requested. That’s reasonable, no?

However, be assured that we will **never** sell or transfer this information to third-party vendors or aggregators. And we won’t ask for any information we don’t absolutely need in order to comply with applicable law or to make your user experience the best it can be.

You’re welcome.

#### Cookies

Like most websites, our sites use cookies to give you the best possible experience. A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. This allows us to improve the overall user experience by identifying and tracking visitors, monitoring their usage of the Codeship website(s) and analyzing website access preferences. By continuing to use the site you agree to our use of cookies. If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, then you should set your browser to refuse cookies before using Codeship’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Codeship’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

####  Cookies

Like pretty much every other website in the 21st century, we use cookies. If you don’t want cookies placed on your computer, you should adjust your browser settings accordingly.

#### Business transfers

If Codeship, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Codeship goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Codeship may continue to use your personal information so long as it complies with the custodial obligations in this policy.

####  Business transfers

We expect to be around for a long, long time. (Whether you like it or not – hah!!) But in case Codeship ceases to operate (or in the event the business is acquired), you acknowledge that any successor may continue to operate according to the service provider obligations in this Privacy Policy.

#### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Codeship and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

####  Ads

You may, from time to time, see ads on the website from third parties. (Hey – we gotta eat too, y’know?) Hopefully the ads aren’t overly intrusive and are consistent with your user experience. Please be aware that some of our ad partners may set cookies that allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time you receive an ad. These cookies are not generated by Codeship. Again, if you don’t want cookies placed, then adjust your browser settings accordingly.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Codeship may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Codeship’s sole discretion. Codeship encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a codeship.com account, you should also check your account’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

####  Privacy Policy Changes

Codeship reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time to account for new policies or regulations. But regardless, your continued use of the site following any change to policy reflects your consent to the modified Privacy Policy terms (if any). Thanks.

#### Change log:

  * 17\. April 2012: [First version](https://gist.github.com/flomotlik/2d6d1e36142014aae089#file-codeship-old-privacy-policy)
  * 23\. September 2014: Second version (current)
